Francis D. Donovan Papers
© 2011 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Photographic materials, undated, 1829-1997
  - Subseries A: Prints, undated, 1829-1997
    - Sub-subseries 1: Stations, undated, 1858-1997
      - West Warwick, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 19:, Folder 1980)
      - Whipple's, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1936 (Box 19:, Folder 1981)
      - Wickford, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 19:, Folder 1982)
      - Wickford Junction, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1939 (Box 19:, Folder 1983)
      - Wickford Junction, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1984)
      - Wickford Junction, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1961 (Box 19:, Folder 1985)
      - Wickford Landing, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1986)
      - Woodlawn, Rhode Island, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1987)
      - Wood River Junction, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1988)
      - Wood River Junction, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1935 (Box 19:, Folder 1989)
      - Wood River Junction, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1912 (Box 19:, Folder 1990)
      - Woodville, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1991)
      - Woonsocket, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1992)
      - Woonsocket, Rhode Island, New York & New England Railroad station, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1993)
      - Woonsocket, Rhode Island, Providence & Worcester Railroad station, 1881 (Box 19:, Folder 1994)
      - Woonsocket, Rhode Island, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad station, 1909 (Box 19:, Folder 1995)
      - Woonsocket, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1912 (Box 19:, Folder 1996)
      - Woonsocket, Rhode Island, Railroad station, 1961 (Box 19:, Folder 1997)
      - Woonsocket, Rhode Island, New Haven Railroad station, 1963 (Box 20:, Folder 1998)
      - Memphis, Tennessee, Louisville & Nashville Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 1999)
      - Memphis, Tennessee, Illinois Central Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2000)
      - Memphis, Tennessee, Southern Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2001)
      - Paris, Tennessee, Louisville & Nashville Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2002)
      - Athens, Texas, Saint Louis Southwestern Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2003)
      - Athens, Texas, Southern Pacific Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2004)
      - Athens, Texas, Saint Louis Southwestern Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2005)
      - Corsicana, Texas, Southern Pacific Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2006)
      - Corsicana, Texas, Texas & Brazos Valley Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2007)
      - Ennis, Texas, Texas Midland Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2008)
      - Lubbock, Texas, Santa Fe Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2009)
      - Marlin, Texas, Southern Pacific Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2010)
      - Marlin, Texas, railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2011)
      - Plainview, Texas, Santa Fe Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2012)
      - Ogden, Utah, railroad station, 1908 (Box 20:, Folder 2013)
      - Branford, Vermont, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1970 (Box 20:, Folder 2014)
      - Chester, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2015)
      - Chester, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2016)
      - Chester, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, 1906 (Box 20:, Folder 2017)
      - Concord, Vermont, Maine Central Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2018)
      - Cuttingsville, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2019)
      - Cuttingsville, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2020)
      - Danby, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 2021)
      - East Concord, Vermont, Maine Central Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2022)
      - Ely, Vermont, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1970 (Box 20:, Folder 2023)
      - Fairlee, Vermont, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2024)
      - Farmington, Vermont, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2025)
      - Gilman, Vermont, Maine Central Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2026)
      - Island Pond, Vermont, Grand Trunk Railroad station, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 2027)
      - Kendall, Vermont, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1970 (Box 20:, Folder 2028)
      - Lunenburg, Vermont, Maine Central Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2029)
      - Miles Pond, Vermont, Maine Central Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2030)
      - Montpelier, Vermont, Central Vermont Railroad station, 1883 (Box 20:, Folder 2031)
      - North Concord, Vermont, Maine Central Railroad station, 1933 (Box 20:, Folder 2032)
      - Putney, Vermont, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 2033)
      - South Shaftsbury, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2034)
      - South Wallingford, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 2035)
      - Summit, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 2036)
      - Wallingford, Vermont, Rutland Railroad station, 1963 (Box 20:, Folder 2037)
      - Wells River, Vermont, Boston & Maine Railroad station, 1970 (Box 20:, Folder 2038)
      - Westminster, Vermont, Boston & Maine Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2039)
      - White River Junction, Vermont, railroad station, 1970 (Box 20:, Folder 2040)
      - Windsor, Vermont, railroad station, 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 2041)
      - Windsor, Vermont, railroad station, 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 2042)
      - Winooski, Vermont, Central Vermont Railroad station, 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 2043)
      - Glanegg, Austria, railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2044)
      - Nova Scotia, Canada; Samson, an English-built steam locomotive (0-6-0) built in 1838 that ran on the Albion Mines Railway in Pictou County, Nova Scotia, from 1839-1893. It is currently owned by the Nova Scotia Museum of Industry and is on static display at the Museum in Stellarton, Nova Scotia. It was mainly a coal-hauler on the mines' six-mile railroad from 1839 to 1867, but also saw service carrying passengers in the primitive coach shown in the photo. Samson was on display beside the Halifax train station until 1950 when it was moved to New Glasgow, Nova Scotia. The coach has also been preserved and may be on display at the Baltimore & Ohio Railroad Museum in Baltimore. Samson is said to be the first locomotive in Canada to run on iron rails, and is the oldest surviving locomotive in Canada, and the only known surviving locomotive of English locomotive pioneer, Timothy Hackworth, who built engines in Durham, England. [this description provided courtesy of Edward Sweeney], undated (Box 28:, Folder 2902)
      - Quebec, Canada, Quebec & Lake Saint John Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2045)
      - Hiwalya, Ceylon, railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2046)
      - Taplaw, England, Great Western Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2047)
      - Darjeeling, India, railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2048)
      - Acamboro, Mexico, National Railroad of Mexico Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2049)
      - Leon, Mexico, National Railroad of Mexico Railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2050)
      - Greymouth, New Zealand, railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2051)
      - Unidentified railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2052)
      - Unidentified railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2053)
      - Unidentified railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2054)
      - Unidentified railroad station, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2055)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Engines, undated, 1829-1997
      - Alaska Railroad, engine 902, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2057)
      - Akron, Canton & Youngstown Railroad, engine 406, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2058)
      - Aroostook Valley Railroad, engine 53, steeple cab freight motor, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2911)
      - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, engine 1403, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2059)
      - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, engine 1800, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2060)
      - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, engine 1805, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2061)
      - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, engine 2007, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2062)
      - Atchinson, Topeka & Santa Fe Railroad, engine 5012, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2063)
      - Ansonia, Derby & Birmingham, very early electric motor, "Old Motor in Pine Rock Park near Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1st freight motor,", 1905 (Box 28:, Folder 2892)
      - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad, engine 55, steam locomotive pushing Russell wing plow during snowstorm at East Millinocket, Maine, 1947 (Box 28:, Folder 2900)
      - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad, engine 65, GP-7, in South Dennis, Massachusetts, 1970 (Box 28:, Folder 2914)
      - Baldwin Locomotive Works Experimental Railroad, "Columbia" (not railroad-owned), undated (Box 27:, Folder 2764)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, "The Columbian", undated (Box 21:, Folder 2187)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, "The Lady Baltimore", undated (Box 21:, Folder 2188)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, "Tom Thumb", undated (Box 21:, Folder 2189)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, engine 1561, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2190)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, engine 3847, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2191)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, engine 5568, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2192)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, engine 7208, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2193)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, engine 7611, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2194)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, engine 7618, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2195)
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, engine 7628, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2196)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 7, 1935 (Box 20:, Folder 2064)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 7, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2065)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 7, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2066)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 7, 1937 (Box 20:, Folder 2067)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 8, 1937 (Box 20:, Folder 2068)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 8, 1937 (Box 20:, Folder 2069)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 8, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2070)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 8, 1938 (Box 20:, Folder 2071)
      - Bath & Hammondsport Railroad, engine 11, 1938 (Box 20:, Folder 2072)
      - Bay Colony Railroad, engine 1063, 1986 (Box 20:, Folder 2073)
      - Bessemer & Lake Erie Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2074)
      - Black Mountain Railroad, engine 1, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2075)
      - Boston & Albany Railroad, engine 204, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2076)
      - Boston & Albany Railroad, engine 276, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2077)
      - Boston & Albany Railroad, engine 432, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2078)
      - Boston & Albany Railroad, engine 543, 1908 (Box 20:, Folder 2079)
      - Boston & Albany Railroad, engine 595, 1920 (Box 20:, Folder 2080)
      - Boston & Lowell Railroad, "Vesta", undated (Box 20:, Folder 2081)
      - Boston & Lynn Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2082)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, "Budd", 1963 (Box 20:, Folder 2083)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, Budd 6155, 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 2084)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, "Flying Yankee", undated (Box 20:, Folder 2085)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 8, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2086)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 110, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2087)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 119, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2088)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 139, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2089)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 260, 1937 (Box 20:, Folder 2090)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 346, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2091)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 443, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2092)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 443, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2093)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 443, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2094)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 443, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2095)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 443, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2096)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 448, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2097)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 448, 1939 (Box 20:, Folder 2098)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 450, undated (Box 20:, Folder 2099)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 494, 1970 (Box 20:, Folder 2100)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 494, 1970 (Box 21:, Folder 2101)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 494, 1997 (Box 21:, Folder 2102)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 494, 1997 (Box 21:, Folder 2103)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 745, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2104)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 779, 1899 (Box 21:, Folder 2105)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 785, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2106)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 904, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2107)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 934, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2108)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 935, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2109)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 969, 1929 (Box 21:, Folder 2110)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 990, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2111)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1008, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2112)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1009, 1912 (Box 21:, Folder 2113)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1038, 1937 (Box 21:, Folder 2114)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1114, 1970 (Box 21:, Folder 2115)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1136 on train 638, circa 1930 (Box 28:, Folder 2831)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1143, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2116)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1399, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2117)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1404, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2118)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1421, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2119)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1421, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2120)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1421, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2121)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1493, circa 1950 (Box 21:, Folder 2122)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1543, 1959 (Box 21:, Folder 2123)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1561, 1970 (Box 21:, Folder 2124)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1561, 1970 (Box 21:, Folder 2125)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 1740, 1963 (Box 21:, Folder 2126)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2074, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2127)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2075, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2128)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2104, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2129)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2115, 1934 (Box 21:, Folder 2130)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2341, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2131)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2358, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2132)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2399, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2133)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2407, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2134)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2654, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2135)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2698, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2136)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 2902, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2137)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3000, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2138)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3241, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2139)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3607, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2140)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3620, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2141)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3621, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2142)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3622, 1937 (Box 21:, Folder 2143)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3622, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2144)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3623, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2145)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3623, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2146)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3625, 1952 (Box 21:, Folder 2147)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3628, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2148)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3634, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2149)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3634, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2150)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3637, 1951 (Box 21:, Folder 2151)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3641, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2152)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3647, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2153)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3651, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2154)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3654, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2155)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3659, 1952 (Box 21:, Folder 2156)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3659, 1952 (Box 21:, Folder 2157)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3664, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2158)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3669, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2159)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3670, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2160)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3672, 1951 (Box 21:, Folder 2161)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3675, 1951 (Box 21:, Folder 2162)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3675, 1951 (Box 21:, Folder 2163)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3687, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2164)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3687, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2165)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3688, 1951 (Box 21:, Folder 2166)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3702, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2167)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3702, 1952 (Box 21:, Folder 2168)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3713, 1960 (Box 21:, Folder 2169)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3715, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2170)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3715, circa 1950 (Box 21:, Folder 2171)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3715, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2172)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3715, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2173)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3715, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2174)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3809, 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 2175)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3811, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2176)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 4005, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2177)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, electric locomotive 5002, at Hoosac Tunnel, Massachusetts, 1938 (Box 29:, Folder 2959)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2178)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2179)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2180)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2181)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, unidentified engine, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2182)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, unidentified engine, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2183)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, unidentified engine, 1939 (Box 21:, Folder 2184)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad, engine 3647, 4-6-2, (cab view), undated (Box 28:, Folder 2847)
      - Boston & Maine Railroad locomotive after wreck of the Marlboro Express on November 26, 1905, in Lincoln, Massachusetts (Box 28:, Folder 2894)
      - Boston & New York Air Line Railroad, engine 5, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2185)
      - Boston & New York City Railroad, "Earthquake", undated (Box 21:, Folder 2186)
      - Boston & Providence Railroad, "Daniel Nason", 1936 (Box 21:, Folder 2197)
      - Boston & Providence Railroad, "David B. Slandish", undated (Box 21:, Folder 2198)
      - Boston & Providence Railroad, "Fred Paine", undated (Box 21:, Folder 2199)
      - Boston & Providence Railroad, "W.W. Woolsey", 1872 (Box 21:, Folder 2200)
      - Boston & Providence Railroad, "Useful", undated (Box 28:, Folder 2903)
      - Boston, Clinton & Fitchburg Railroad, "F.B. Fay", undated (Box 21:, Folder 2201)
      - Boston, Hoosac Tunnel & Western Railroad, engine 5, undated (Box 21:, Folder 2202)
      - Boston, Lowell & Northern Railroad, "Suffolk", undated (Box 21:, Folder 2203)
      - Boston, Revere Beach & Lynn Railroad, engine 2, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2204)
      - Boston, Revere Beach & Lynn Railroad, engine 4, undated (Box 27:, Folder 2796)
      - Brimstone Railroad, engine 35, 1960 (Box 22:, Folder 2205)
      - Brookline Railroad, "Brookline", undated (Box 22:, Folder 2206)
      - Burlington Railroad, engines 945 and 9012, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2207)
      - Burlington & Missouri River Railroad, engine 35, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2208)
      - Cape Cod Central Railroad, "Highland Light", undated (Box 22:, Folder 2209)
      - Camp Manufacturing Company Railroad, engine 50, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2210)
      - Canadian National Railroad, engine 6400, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2211)
      - Canadian Pacific Railroad, "Royal Train", undated (Box 22:, Folder 2212)
      - Canadian Pacific Railroad, engine 856, undated (cyanotype) (Box 22:, Folder 2213)
      - Canadian Pacific Railroad, engines 1969 and 3525, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2214)
      - Canadian Pacific Railroad, engine 2838, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2215)
      - Canadian Pacific Railroad, engine 5182, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2216)
      - Central New England Railroad, engine 220, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2217)
      - Central New England Railroad, engine 403, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2218)
      - Central New England Railroad, engines 351 and 451, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2219)
      - Central of Georgia Railroad, engine 454, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2220)
      - Central of Georgia Railroad, engine 1191, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2221)
      - Central Vermont Railroad, engine 214, 1906 (Box 22:, Folder 2222)
      - Chatham & Lebanon Valley Railroad, engine 3, 1854 (Box 22:, Folder 2223)
      - Chemins de Fer de l'Est (French), engines 3264 and 3273, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2840)
      - Chemins de Fer de l'État (French), engine 141-037, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2855)
      - Chemins de Fer de l'État (French), engine 230-167, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2856)
      - Chemins de Fer de l'État (French), engine 230-764, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2857)
      - Chemin de Fer de Paris à Orléans (French), 4-6-2 on passenger train, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2869)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 490, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2224)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 491, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2225)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 500, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2226)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 500, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2227)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 500, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2228)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 875, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2229)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 1600, 1942 (Box 22:, Folder 2230)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 1603, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2231)
      - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad, engine 2786, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2232)
      - Chicago & Alton Railroad, "Huntington", undated (Box 22:, Folder 2233)
      - Chicago & Alton Railroad, engine 47, 1885 (Box 22:, Folder 2234)
      - Chicago & Alton Railroad, engine 47, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2235)
      - Chicago & Alton Railroad, engine 5278, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2236)
      - Chicago & Eastern Illinois Railroad, engine 1008, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2237)
      - Chicago & Illinois Midland Railroad, engine 752, undated (Box 22:, Folder 2238)